<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[iCloud]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>iCloud</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:15:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:15:26 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Settlement 12 World Primer]]></title><description><![CDATA[Several hundred years ago, an event known as the Great Eruption caused the functional collapse of the society of the old world. The new world is built on the technological and cultural remnants of the old world, but it also incorporates the newly-emerged neoscience, also known as magic.The continent that contains Settlement 12 has various regions. From west to east, they are:A long coast, boreal in the north and subtropical in the south. Has several major cities, including San Júpiter and Lacey City.A mountain range not far from the west coast.A large desert between the Norilla Minors and the Norilla Majors. Because of how dry it is, there are few landmarks in this region-most trains travel right though it without stopping.A mountain range east of the Expanse, this mountain range is significantly taller and larger than the Norilla Minors. It is littered with traditional Jovian communities.A vast grassland east of the Norilla Majors. Settlement 12 is on its west edge, while the central grasslands have many farming communities.The farther east one travels, the more toxic the air, water and soil become. On the eastern Solar Plains, farming is difficult. East of that is a hardy forested region known as the Deadlands because of its environmental hostility. The continent-wide railroad lines end in the west Deadlands, where some people scrape out a meager living in the short term (staying here for longer than a year or two can have serious health impacts). The eastern Deadlands are completely uninhabitable, and only receive occasional visits from archeologists looking to study its copious old world ruins.]]></description><link>settlement-12-world-primer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Settlement 12 RPG/Settlement 12 World Primer.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:05:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>